<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="@color/home_background"
    tools:context=".linkdin_activity">

    <androidx.cardview.widget.CardView
        android:id="@+id/cardView17"
        android:layout_width="0dp"
        android:layout_height="200dp"
        android:layout_marginStart="10dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="-15dp"
        android:layout_marginEnd="10dp"
        android:backgroundTint="@color/bg"
        app:cardCornerRadius="20dp"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent">

        <androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent">

            <androidx.cardview.widget.CardView
                android:id="@+id/cardView16"
                android:layout_width="100dp"
                android:layout_height="100dp"
                android:layout_marginStart="30dp"
                android:background="@color/white"
                android:backgroundTint="@color/white"
                app:cardCornerRadius="10dp"
                app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent">

                <ImageView
                    android:id="@+id/imageView17"
                    android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:layout_marginLeft="2dp"
                    android:layout_marginTop="2dp"
                    app:srcCompat="@drawable/icons8_linkedin_96" />
            </androidx.cardview.widget.CardView>

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView13"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:fontFamily="@font/roboto_slab_bold"
                android:text="Linkdin"
                android:textColor="@color/heading_cl"
                android:textSize="30dp"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="@+id/cardView16"
                app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintStart_toEndOf="@+id/cardView16"
                app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="@+id/cardView16" />
        </androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>
    </androidx.cardview.widget.CardView>

    <androidx.cardview.widget.CardView
        android:id="@+id/cardView18"
        android:layout_width="0dp"
        android:layout_height="430dp"
        android:layout_marginStart="30dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="50dp"
        android:layout_marginEnd="30dp"
        android:background="@color/white"
        android:backgroundTint="@color/white"
        app:cardCornerRadius="5dp"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@+id/cardView17">

        <ScrollView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:layout_margin="10dp"
            android:background="@color/white"
            android:backgroundTint="@color/white">

            <androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content">

                <TextView
                    android:id="@+id/textView15"
                    android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:text="LinkedIn (/lɪŋktˈɪn/) is a business and employment-focused social media platform that works through websites and mobile apps. It was launched on May 5, 2003.[6] Since December 2016, it has been a wholly owned subsidiary of Microsoft.[7] The platform is primarily used for professional networking and career development, and allows jobseekers to post their CVs and employers to post jobs. From 2015 most of the company's revenue came from selling access to information about its members to recruiters and sales professionals.[8] LinkedIn has more than 970 million registered members from over 200 countries and territories.[9]  LinkedIn allows members (both workers and employers) to create profiles and connect with each other in an online social network which may represent real-world professional relationships. Members can invite anyone (whether an existing member or not) to become a connection. LinkedIn can also be used to organize offline events, join groups, write articles, publish job postings, post photos and videos, and more.The company was founded in December 2002 by Reid Hoffman and the founding team members from PayPal and Socialnet.com (Allen Blue, Eric Ly, Jean-Luc Vaillant, Lee Hower, Konstantin Guericke, Stephen Beitzel, David Eves, Ian McNish, Yan Pujante, Chris Saccheri).[24] In late 2003, Sequoia Capital led the Series A investment in the company.[25] In August 2004, LinkedIn reached 1 million users.[26] In March 2006, LinkedIn achieved its first month of profitability.[26] In April 2007, LinkedIn reached 10 million users.[26] In February 2008, LinkedIn launched a mobile version of the site.[27]  In June 2008, Sequoia Capital, Greylock Partners, and other venture capital firms purchased a 5% stake in the company for $53 million, giving the company a post-money valuation of approximately $1 billion.[28] In November 2009, LinkedIn opened its office in Mumbai[29] and soon thereafter in Sydney, as it started its Asia-Pacific team expansion. In 2010, LinkedIn opened an International Headquarters in Dublin, Ireland,[30] received a $20 million investment from Tiger Global Management LLC at a valuation of approximately $2 billion,[31] announced its first acquisition, Mspoke,[32] and improved its 1% premium subscription ratio.[33] In October of that year, Silicon Valley Insider ranked the company No. 10 on its Top 100 List of most valuable startups.[34] By December, the company was valued at $1.575 billion in private markets.[35] LinkedIn started its India operations in 2009 and a major part of the first year was dedicated to understanding professionals in India and educating members to leverage LinkedIn for career development.LinkedIn filed for an initial public offering in January 2011. The company traded its first shares on May 19, 2011, under the NYSE symbol &quot;LNKD&quot;, at $45 (~$58.00 in 2022) per share.[36] Shares of LinkedIn rose as much as 171% on their first day of trade on the New York Stock Exchange and closed at $94.25, more than 109% above IPO price. Shortly after the IPO, the site's underlying infrastructure was revised to allow accelerated revision-release cycles.[13] In 2011, LinkedIn earned $154.6 million in advertising revenue alone, surpassing Twitter, which earned $139.5 million.[37] LinkedIn's fourth-quarter 2011, earnings soared because of the company's increase in success in the social media world.[38] By this point, LinkedIn had about 2,100 full-time employees compared to the 500 that it had in 2010.[39]  In April 2014, LinkedIn announced that it had leased 222 Second Street, a 26-story building under construction in San Francisco's SoMa district, to accommodate up to 2,500 of its employees,[40] with the lease covering 10 years.[41] The goal was to join all San Francisco-based staff (1,250 as of January 2016) in one building, bringing sales and marketing employees together with the research and development team.[41] In March 2016 they started to move in.[41] In February 2016 following an earnings report, LinkedIn's shares dropped 43.6% within a single day, down to $108.38 per share. LinkedIn lost $10 billion of its market capitalization that day."
                    android:textColor="@color/black"
                    app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
                    app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
                    app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
                    app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent" />
            </androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>
        </ScrollView>
    </androidx.cardview.widget.CardView>

    <androidx.cardview.widget.CardView
        android:layout_width="0dp"
        android:layout_height="100dp"
        android:layout_marginStart="10dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="50dp"
        android:layout_marginEnd="10dp"
        android:backgroundTint="@color/bg"
        app:cardCornerRadius="20dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@+id/cardView18" >

        <androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent">

            <Button
                android:id="@+id/ln_btn"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:backgroundTint="#f7a072"
                android:text="Linkdin"
                android:textColor="@color/black"
                app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent" />
        </androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>
    </androidx.cardview.widget.CardView>
</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>